what's up with my people like this there's another
qué pasa a mi gente como esta hay otro
video today on the videos today and
vídeo hoy en los vídeos hoy y
probably even on live it's me who's
seguramente incluso a la directo soy yo
jumping out of my skin found
el que me salgo del pellejo encontrado
this figure yesterday my wife thinks it's a
esta figura ayer mi mujer se cree que es
joke but I'm going to buy it are you
broma pero me la voy a comprar estáis
looking at this [ __ ] figure that you're
viendo esta [__] figura que estáis
looking at this [ __ ] figure up close this [ __ ] figure
viendo esta [__] figura de cerca esta
measures the same as me this
[__] figura mide lo mismo que yo esta
[ __ ] figure has the same size as me
[__] figura tiene lo mismo que yo
ok there's another one of buzz lightyear that's a
ok hay otra de buzz lightyear que es un
little shorter but it's not going to
poco más bajita pero es que no me van a
fit them all I'm already thinking of
caber todos ya tengo pensamientos de
buying that one and putting it there and I have to
comprar esa y ponerla ahí y tengo que
make a lot of videos to be able to buy it
hacer muchos vídeos para poder comprarla
okay I don't have to I don't have to make a
valente no tengo que no tengo que hacer
lot of videos and maybe I'll have to sell
muchos vídeos y tal vez tenga que vender
an organ or something like that I don't know
un órgano o algo por el estilo no lo sé
by the way speaking of disney I know you're
por cierto hablando de disney
asking me a lot
sé que me estáis preguntando muchísimo
why I don't do a review of the movie
porque no hago una review de la película
moulin in the action that was released
moulin en la acción que se estrenó hace
weeks ago not on Friday this one not the
semanas no el viernes este no
other one okay a week and a half almost two
el otro vale semana y media casi dos
weeks a week and a half well I'm not doing it
semanas semana y media pues no la hago
because I'm just excited to be Latino
porque nada más se ilusiona ser latino
the movie I didn't like the truth
la película no me ha gustado la verdad
is it's not that it's [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
no es que sea una [__] [__] [__]
absolute [ __ ]  but the truth is that it is
[__] absoluta pero la verdad que es
quite mediocre I did not like the
bastante mediocre no me ha gustado la
movie at all just like the day that
peli para nada igual que el día que
Aladir I went to see it at the cinema like seven or
aladir fui a verla al cine como siete u
eight times this one I emulated it bought and I
ocho veces esta de emularla comprado y
will never see it again in my [ __ ] life
no la voy a ver más en mi [__] vida
surely it is that I found it tacky
seguramente es que me pareció cutre
sincerely no no I did not like it I did not like it just like
sinceramente no no no me ha gustado no
I did not like
me ha gustado igual que tampoco me gustó
Beauty and the Beast very much' where the
mucho la bella y la bestia' que la
beast looked like an animatronic from
bestia parecía un animatronic de
Cortylandia or rather from the beast from the
cortylandia o sea de la bestia de las
Disneyland parades they are better
cabalgatas de disneylandia están mejor
made than that one you know Chelsea and Mule
hecha que esa que sabéis chelsea y mula
were
fue
the costumes that the
los trajes con los que van vencido los
citizens are defeated in look like Pixar's but
ciudadanos parecen de pichardo pero
you do not know what it is like to step into Pixar
usted no sabe lo que es pisar de pixar
from a costume store here
de una tienda de disfraces aquí
exhibition previously to much because
exhibición anteriomente a mucho porque
because I did not want to be like the
porque no quería ser como la de
animated one no because I wanted to make it
animación no porque quería hacerla como
more real since you leave the movie as
más real ya que dejas la película como
more based on the true story it is not the
más basada en el cuento real no es la
true story that comes to be the
historia real que viene a ser la
most realistic movie but then you see
película más realista pero luego te ves
Mule doing Matrix which is like this he
a mula haciendo matriz que es así salta
suddenly jumps on top of a wall from the
de repente en lo alto de una pared de la
wall he goes to a beam and from the beam he puts
pared va a una viga y de la viga le mete
a  flying kick to a spear that's over
una patada voladora a una lanza que hay
there and it goes for the bad guy's chest
por ahí y va para el pecho del malo
super realistic they've made the movie
súper realista que han hecho la película
and nothing talking about movie to
y nada hablando de película para
movie what's mounted here my
película la que está montada aquí mi
friend luisito communicates with his other with
compi luisito comunica con su otro con
rays sincerely I was watching the
rayitos sinceramente me estuve viendo el
clip of a mouth that I now visit
clip de un boca que ahora visito
communication has a podcast channel and
comunicación tiene un canal de podcast y
is also dedicated to doing little time
se dedica también a hacer poca vez
entering the dick with the podcast poka
entrando a la [__] con los podcast poka
poka poka the only authentic
poka poka el único vodka auténtico de
quality vodka and from a guy who is very good
calidad y de un tío que está buenísimo
is the one from this channel I do
es el de este canal
n't know him at all but
no lo conozco de nada pero tenéis que
you have to subscribe because the guy is super hot and it's glorious to listen to him what I was saying is dedicated to the communicator visits a podcast program that has premiered and it seems that each week will have a guest and this week it was
tendrá un invitado y en esta semana le
his friend's turn well his friend
ha tocado a su amigo bueno a su amigo
who has become his friend again now
que ha vuelto a ser su amigo ahora
because they have spent a year without speaking to each other
porque se han pegado un año sin hablarse
rayito from ryan show and there they have done the one about
rayito de ryan show y ahí han hecho la
the image cleaning telling
de la de la limpieza de imagen contando
a story and telling in a story that you
un cuento y contando en una historia que
look popular would have been
miras popular hubiera viene de [__]
great the story but for a post
madre la historia pero para un post
carlo and  he quoted as if it hasn't worked
carlo y citó como que no ha colado de
like well actually it has worked
como que bueno en realidad se ha colado
because there are a lot of people who are so blind
porque hay mucha gente que es tan ciega
and surely at this point in the
y seguramente ya a estas alturas del
video which I will be like a minute and a half
vídeo que llevaré como un minuto y medio
or two minutes into the video white call is
o dos minutos de vídeo llama blanca es
Calvin like but look honestly if it was
calvin like pero mira sinceramente si se
about
tratase
favoritism or things like that I have to
favoritismo o cosas por el estilo tengo
say what honestly I dislike
que decir lo que sinceramente me cae
lippe rodríguez and va la voz which is [ __ ]
lippe rodríguez y va la voz que es [__]
[ __ ] if it was a question of favoritism
[__] si fuera cuestión del favoritismo
then I wouldn't support live but
pues no apoyaría live pero es que
honestly seeing everything the
sinceramente viendo todo todo el clic
whole click and the string of lies that they
completo y la sarta de mentiras que
spew and contradictions and I know
sueltan y de contradicciones y que sé
that they are wide and you where have you
que están anchos y usted donde habéis
eaten well I have to that objective and I
comido pues yo tengo que ese objetivo y
have to do my job here and spew
tengo que hacer aquí mi trabajo y soltar
the nonsense and not on this occasion it is about tion
la mandanga y no en esta ocasión se
you lie honestly atmosphere
trata ción mientes sinceramente ambiente
watch the full video okay I'm going to
mirarlo el vídeo completo vale os lo voy
ask you please watch the
a pedir por favor mirad el vídeo
full video and once you see the
completo y una vez que veáis el vídeo
full video you will see your opinion but I
completo veréis vuestra opinión pero
think I'm going to get with me that
creo que vaya a conseguir conmigo en que
these people lie more than they talk but not
esta gente miente más que habla pero no
that the more they talk because
que mientras más que habla porque lo
I say so and not only because of the evidence that  I'm
diga yo y no solamente por las pruebas
going to show you that they're
que os voy a mostrar es que están
saying things that are contrary to what they
diciendo cosas que son contrarias a las
said last year, that is to say,
que dijeron el año pasado o sea es que
they themselves have taken us
ellos mismos ellos mismos nos han tomado
for idiots that yes, I am an
por [__] que sí que yo soy
idiot for you I'm not going to put a
[__] por ustedes no voy a poner un
little bit of context okay context more
poquito en contexto vale contexto más
I answered more like calling my friend Juan
contestó más como llamar a mi amigo juan
Warning
warning
I know that surely all of you who are
yo sé que seguramente todo lo que estáis
coming to this video know the whole
llegando a este vídeo sabéis toda la
story from last year but I'm going to
historia del año pasado pero la voy a
refresh it anyway you have a
refrescar de todas maneras tenéis un
very nice and very precious clue here
indicio muy bonito y muy precioso aquí
below on the youtube line and you can go
abajo en la línea de youtube y podéis ir
jumping to the topic that comes out of the channel
saltando al tema que os salga del canal
the thing is that the rayito as
la cosa es que el rayito como lo llaman
his colleagues call him as he is affectionately called,
sus colegas como se le llama de cariño
collaborated with Badajoz on
hacía colaboraciones con badajoz en
numerous occasions not only in this
numerosas ocasiones no solamente en este
video that he recorded with live
vídeo que grabó con live
but when he recorded this video with live
pero cuando grabó el vídeo este con live
the live he made the one of checking his cell phone
el live le hizo la de revisarle el móvil
you know what about putting unfaithful and it
ya sabéis lo de poniendo infieles y
seems that he reads some messages that could be
parece que lee unos mensajes que podrían
from Luisito Comunica talking about a
ser de luisito comunica hablando de una
girl that he slept with yesterday yesterday
morra que se tiró ayer de ayer
yesterday
ayer
the social networks were filled at that time
se llenaron por aquel entonces las redes
both from Visito Comunica and
sociales tanto del visito comunica como
from  her cool novel of
la de su novela chule de comentarios de
all kinds of comments to luisito comunica calling him
todo tipo a luisito comunica diciéndole
unfaithful and this type of things and to the cool one
infiel y este tipo de cosas y a la chule
well of the type realize friend no and in
pues del tipo date cuenta amiga no y a
turn to rayito well everyone
su vez a rayito pues todo el mundo
hating the many calling him a traitor
odiando los muchísimos llamando traidor
no that he had sold his friend for 500
no que había vendido a su amigo por 500
pesos which the translation to 500 pesos is
pesos que la traducción a 500 pesos son
25 euros or rather that he sells him cheap
25 euros o sea que lo vende barato
after that video was published in
después de publicarse ese vídeo en el
which supposedly live rodríguez
que supuestamente live rodríguez no se
had not realized because he had not
había dado cuenta porque no lo había
reviewed it and had not realized that they
revisado y no se había dado cuenta de
exposed luisito comunica she
que exponían a luisito comunica ella lo
quickly deleted it and uploaded a video
borró corriendo y subió un vídeo
asking him for forgiveness but she asked him for forgiveness
pidiéndole perdón pero le pedía perdón
for having exposed him and for having
por haberlo expuesto y por haberlo
included him in the video and that he had been
metido en el vídeo y que se haya visto
splashed at no time denying
salpicado en ningún momento desmentir
the messages that she had read a week
los mensajes que había leído a la semana
because yes he was silent for a [ __ ] week
porque sí estuvo una [__] semana callado
the raya appeared in his
el raya salió en su historia de
instagram story showing what
instagram mostrando lo que venía a ser
the conversation was and it could be understood that
la conversación y se podía entender que
he
él
from my point of view without bad
desde mi punto de vista sin mala
intention because I think it can happen
intención porque creo que puede pasarse
you are reading conversations read the
tú estás leyendo conversaciones lees el
username read the message  from
nombre del usuario lee el mensaje de
another message reading messages reading
otro mensaje va leyendo mensajes leyendo
messages finally jump to the result of the
mensajes salte al fin al resultado del
video it has been a little strange I think it
vídeo ha quedado un poco raro yo creo
could have been some kind of
que pudo ser toda una especie de
misunderstanding okay when reading it when
malentendido vale a la hora de leerlo a
interpreting it and when they did
la hora de interpretarlo y a la hora de
not clarify things well you can
que no aclararon las cosas bien pueden
see this is the conversation that
ver esta es la conversación que leyó
Lizbeth read in the video I sent this
lizbeth en el vídeo yo le envié este
video to Louis it is a video that
vídeo a louis es un vídeo que me envió
a girl sent me with whom I went out the day
pues una chica con la cual salí un día
before the truth is and I forwarded this
antes la verdad y yo le reenvía este
video to Louis and I told him that I said the
vídeo a louis y le puse la que me echo
day before yesterday I did it I sent it to
que antier yo lo hice yo se lo mandé a
him
él
to which he responded to me all this that you
a lo cual él me respondió todo esto que
see here and this is the conversation I don't
ven aquí y esta es la conversación yo no
really know Lizbeth because she took
sé realmente lizbeth porque sacó de
things out of context and said Luisito the
contexto las cosas y dijo luisito el
rascal the one who caught me on land that was what
pillo la que me cogía en tierra eso fue
she said in the video and the truth
lo que dijo ella en el vídeo y la verdad
is that it was not like that it
es que no fue así
would be more or less clarified that it had
quedaría más o menos aclarada en que
all been a misunderstanding
todo había sido un malentendido a la
when reading the screenshots what
hora de leer las capturas qué es lo que
happens is that a few months later live
pasa que a los pocos meses live
Rodriguez gives an interview to give the
rodríguez da una entrevista a dar la
review
review
and says the following comes out saved
y dice lo siguiente sale salva
I know that it is not with this intention I
yo sé que no lo esté con esta intención
read a message no if I never say
lo leí un mensaje no si yo nunca digo
this said it yesterday all my young man
esto lo dijo ayer todo mi joven
really would have a hard time telling you
realmente me costaría decirte
exactly but I am almost sure
exactamente pero yo estoy casi segura
that that conversation for a group and
que esa conversación para un grupo y
well it
bueno
was individual is false
era individual es falsa
and cut the best until I
y recortar lo mejor hasta que yo me
shut up because honestly we
callé porque sinceramente
can not do anything else simply
ya no podemos hacer más nada simplemente
believe one thing or believe the other yes it is
creer una cosa o creer la otra sí que es
true that well the screenshot
verdad que bueno la captura de pantalla
today of whatsapp unless they
hoy en día de whatsapp a no ser que
include audios we cannot believe them or
incluyan audios no las podemos creer o
not because today whatsapp is
no porque ya hoy en día el whatsapp se
manipulated whatsapp is hacked and the
manipula el whatsapp se piratea y los
guasa can be modified and they can be
guasa se puede modificar y te pueden
showing you a conversation on a
estar enseñando una conversación en un
cell phone moving the participant or putting it
móvil moviendo la participaba o metiendo
in the message and that is modified
en el mensajito y que este modificado
so here each one what you want to
entonces aquí ya cada uno lo que quieras
believe evidently there is one thing that
creer evidentemente hay una cosa que
always happens on the network and that is that
siempre pasa en la red y es que queda
the one with the most support looks better libre
mejor el que tiene más apoyo libre
rodríguez has made many be given to
rodríguez ha hecho muchas ser dadas a
many people therefore he has a
mucha gente por lo tanto tiene una
shitty reputation accompanied with the
reputación de [__] acompañada con la
shitty reputation that he has for the
reputación de [__] que tiene para la
bomb we take for granted that it was the
bomba damos por cierto que era el canal
all Spanish speaking channel with forty and  so
todo de habla hispana con cuarenta y
many millions of subscribers and they have the
tantos millones de suscriptores y tienen
same views as the crazy mother of
las mismas visitas que la madre loca de
we hate it's good basically there is that
we hate es bueno básicamente hay en que
no the story ok it was assumed that
no la historia vale se suponía que
lisbeth had read those conversations
lisbeth había leído esas conversaciones
wrong I think it wasn't on purpose I think it does
mal yo creo que no fue aposta yo creo
n't look like it was
que no tiene pinta de ser
intentional in fact we see that it was not with
intencionado de hecho vemos que no con
bad intentions and that rayo doesn't even
mala intención y que el rayo ni se da
realize no then I simply think
cuenta no entonces simplemente yo creo
that it is a misunderstanding okay as
que se trata de un malentendido vale por
much as the voice goes how nice the move
mucho que va la voz sea bonito la movida
is I think that when reading it he didn't do it on
está yo creo que al leerlo no lo hizo a
purpose and I think that the editor
posta y yo creo que tampoco el editor
as such is not aware of these things
como tal está en cuenta de estas cosas
either because in the end a person who is
sea porque al cabo una persona que está
editing I have editors and they meditate on what
editando yo tengo editores y meditan lo
I sent them this and what you see and
que yo le mandé esto ya lo que tú veas y
how they review our pop video or something like that
como nos revisen su el vídeo pop o algo
that for my part I would leave it as a
así que por mi parte yo lo dejaría en un
misunderstanding okay the case and the problem
malentendido vale el caso y el problema
is that rayito came out the week that it
es que rayito salió a la semana que
took a [ __ ] week to come out to
tardó una [__] semana en salir a
deny fact and save the ass of the
desmentir hecho y salvarle el culo al
public colleague that compensation that
colega público esa compensación que
supposedly they had read it wrong but
supuestamente la habían leído mal pero
then live in the interview he says that it is that
es que luego live en la entrevista dice
she did not or that  I would swear it
que es que ella no o que juraría que no
wasn't a conversation between given that I would
era una conversación entre dado que
swear it was a group but well
juraría que era un grupo pero bueno
let's see what they said in
vamos a ver qué es lo que han dicho en
the forest because I think they are lying
el bosque porque pienso que mienten
outright okay I think they have
rotundamente vale yo creo que se han
made up a story that they would love to have
montado una película que ya la quisieran
Louis spends
louis entera me pasa
the whole night collecting evidence so
la noche recopilando pruebas así que por
please look at them before judging because on
favor mirarlas antes de juzgar porque en
this channel we don't talk for the sake of talking and of
este canal no se habla por hablar y por
course before continuing if this is the
supuesto antes de seguir si es la
first time you visit this channel and you didn't
primera vez que visita este canal y no
know me click on subscribe right now
me conocía dale ahora mismo a suscribir
I want everyone who sees this
quiero que todo el mundo que ve este
video to subscribe why did you agree to
vídeo se suscriba por qué accediste a
record with well with the most
grabar con pues con la el canal más
controversial channel most sensationalist controversial in the
polémico más amarillista polémico de del
country know your serve what happened there well
país sabe su saque que sucedió ahí bueno
here I don't either the intentions not the
aquí yo no tampoco ya las intenciones no
plan that he has not the move that he's
del plan que tiene no de la movida que
going to talk about because of course these
va a hablar porque por supuesto estos
two who have been very good friends for
dos que han sido muy amigos desde hace
like nine or ten years
como nueve o diez años
these two before sitting down for the podcast
estos dos antes de sentarse del podcast
have prepared more or less what they were going to
han prepara más o menos lo que iban a
talk about and here I see the intentions already
hablar y yo aquí veo las intenciones ya
where you are going I want to make it very clear
por dónde vas quiero dejar muy claro
okay I want that not that this has no
vale quiero que no que esto no tenga
room for misinterpretation but at
lugar a malinterpretaciones pero en
no time do I defend or  I justify
ningún momento defiendo ni justifico
Havana voice for mockery has done many
habana voz para burla ha hecho muchas
things to my colleagues and they are [ __ ] [ __ ]
cosas a colegas míos y son [__] [__]
you have a lot of criticism on this channel
tenéis en este canal un montón de
Havana bots but things as they
críticas habana bots pero las cosas como
are these
son estos
have a tinge making too much incisive
tiene un tinte haciendo demasiado inciso
taking advantage of Barbón's bad reputation
aprovechando la mala reputación de
as if they suffer too much it
barbón como que lo sufren demasiado me
makes me laugh a lot that he says how I agreed to
hace mucha gracia que diga cómo accedí a
collaborate with the most sensationalist channel
colaborar con el canal más amarillista
in the country when I do not consider it to be the
del país cuando no considero que sea el
most sensationalist channel in the country it may
canal más amarillista del país ya puede
be sexist sensationalist [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
ser machista sensacionalista [__] [__]
scum of people but the most there
[__] escoria de gente pero el más los
are worse I can tell you so that it
hay peores te puedo decir así que se le
comes to your head quickly more final tv
venga a la cabeza rápido más final tv
mafia cntv is a channel from Mexico that has been saying
mafia cntv es un canal de méxico que se
all year that the
ha pegado todo el año diciendo que el
coronavirus was an experiment by the USA
coronavirus era un experimento de eeuu
to attack China but then it
para atacar a china pero luego le ha
went wrong and the virus escaped
salido mal y se le ha escapado el virus
and that then it was prepared for I started
y que luego estaba preparado por empecé
no well a move a movie that
no pues una movida una película que
told the note and that channel has profited
contó el nota y ese canal se ha lucrado
from a lot of quite strong moves
de un montón de movida bastante fuertes
in the form of big cases of
en plan de casos gordos de
disappearances of aggressions us and
desapariciones de agresiones nosotros y
channels like  in mexico there's one how much is it
canales como es en mexico hay uno cuánto
worth
vale
well I've known the people from bala
bueno pues yo a las personas de bala
boom for years
boom las conozco desde hace años
you know I've known them since
tú sabes yo los conozco desde hace desde
the word went out to the big
que va la voz fuera a la gran empresa de
video company and well known well I already knew them
videos y conocida pues yo ya los conocía
since they made little memes for
desde que hacían pequeños memes para
facebook and all that and I knew them I
facebook y todo eso y yo los conocía me
went with them and had a good
iba con ellos y llevaba una buena
working relationship with them so they
relación de trabajo con ellos entonces
asked me to collaborate with them on
me pidieron que colaborara con ellos en
different occasions and new problems
distintas ocasiones y nuevos problemas
never until this occasion when lizbeth invited me
nunca hasta esta ocasión que me invitó
to collaborate with her and in what I would do
lizbeth a colaborar con ella y en lo que
saying I find it very funny
haría diciendo me resulta muy gracioso
that luisito I asked him how he agreed
que luisito le pregunté que cómo accedió
to collaborate with the check but without if you
a colaborar con el cheque pero sin si
are friends already rayito had been
sois amigos ya rayito llevaba años
collaborating with boom bands for years it wasn't the
colaborando con bandas boom no era la
first time they had already made
primera vez habían hecho ya una decena
at least a dozen collaboration videos on
por lo menos de vídeo de colaboración en
your channel on the other channel of
tu canal en el canal del otro del canal
the diverse channel they had crossed a lot
de la diversa se habían cruzado montón
of collaborations and you who was his friend his
de colaboraciones y tú que era su amigo
best friend didn't know but well
su mejor amigo no lo sabía pero bueno
this is not a lie in itself okay since
esto no es una mentira en sí vale ya que
the catch to the distracted homicide who has
la [__] al homicidio distraído que se
lost his mind for one of the
le ha ido el pensamiento para uno de los
risks are many laughs the air
riesgos son muchos risas el aire
lizbeth begins to  read the messages and
lizbeth se pone a leer los mensajes y
reads them as she wants
los lee como como ella quiere
living like this and I am far away without
viviendo así y yo estoy de lejos sin
bitterness but knowing everything but
amargura sino sabiendo todo pero
really because she made a mistake in
realmente ya pues se equivocó en la
reading the messages in the writing it
lectura de los mensajes en la redacción
is wrong and it was as I noticed in account
está mal y fue como yo noté en cuenta
and since I never saw that video they never
y como nunca vi ese vídeo nunca me lo
sent it to me we could think badly and think
mandaron podríamos pensar mal y pensar
how good that in the confusion they
que qué bueno que en la confusión la
did it on purpose that not only the
hicieron aposta que no solamente el
editor put that in the video but
editor metido eso en el vídeo sino que
also that they see it they would have reviewed it and
además les ve lo hubiese revisado y lo
put it in on purpose to generate controversy
metió aposta para generar la polémica
but we have to recognize that it is normal
pero tenemos que reconocer que es normal
okay it is a misunderstanding that can occur
vale es un malentendido que se puede dar
and that's it imagine that you search for a
y ya está imaginaros que buscáis una
word in the whatsapp search engine and you
palabra en el buscador de whatsapp y os
get the entire list of messages from
sale toda la lista de mensajes de todo
everyone you were not reading the same thing read
el mundo no ibais leyendo lo mismo leer
a username how
un nombre de usuario qué tal
can they be misinterpreted six months
se pueden malinterpretar seis meses
later or like months later I thought
después o como meses después yo pensé
that since he was not going to upload the video you
que ya que ni el vídeo lo iba a subir
know
sabes
four or six months later he publishes it and
cuatro o seis meses después lo publica y
without telling me anything without sending me anything
sin decirme nada sin mandarme nada
because it was already old not having in
porque era era ya viejo no al tener en
six months I had ram it is something like that so
seis meses tenía ram es es algo así
when he sends it to me when I see
entonces cuando me lo manda cuando veo
the public video
el vídeo público
which was the same day that my  Dad
que fue el mismo día que fallece mi papá
had a pretty horrible day
estuvo bastante un día horrible
Barack and that's how the lies start
barack y así empiezan las mentiras
straight away okay he says it was an
directamente vale dice que fue un vídeo
old video that was recorded like six
antiguo que lo grabaron hace como seis
months ago and suddenly he made it public and that he
meses y de repente lo público y que lo
posted it on the very same day of
publicó precisamente el mismo día de la
his father's death when I
muerte de su padre esto a mí cuando lo
saw him live reacting without having
vi en directo reaccionando sin haber
investigated well the truth is it made me
investigado pues la verdad me dio mal
think badly knowing the trajectory
que pensar ya conociendo la trayectoria
of bala voz and the pigs of while they are
de bala voz y los cerdos de mientras que
I said [ __ ]
son yo dije [__] [__]
these people had the video saved
esta gente tenía el vídeo ahí guardado
they saw that it was Rayito's moment that
vieron que era el momento de rayito que
was trending because
estaba en tendencias porque se acababa
his parents had just died and that day they
de morir sus padres y ese día pues
were talking about him and they took advantage of the
estaban hablando de él y aprovecharon
father's death dad
ahí el fallecimiento del padre papá
schoolboy the video that the video had
escolar el vídeo que el vídeo tuviera
more views no what a [ __ ] pig how ugly
más visitas no que [__] cerdo que en feo
because surely he had that video
porque seguramente ese vídeo lo tuviera
saved
guardado
or rather Rayito leave today because
o sea rayito excendencia hoy porque se
his father died
ha muerto su padre
but it turns out that it's a
pero es que resulta ser que que es
lie that's a lie neither the video was
mentira que es mentira ni el vídeo era
recorded six months ago nor the video was
grabado hace seis meses ni el vídeo lo
published the same day of
publicaron el mismo día de la muerte del
Rayito's father's death I don't want to give them
padre de rayito no me las quiero dar
from here I give you my condolences Rayito I'm
desde aquí te doy mi pésame rayito lo
so sorry it must be very hard
siento muchísimo tiene que ser muy duro
losing your father from here my
perder a tu padre desde aquí mi pésame
heartfelt condolences but as I was saying, I've been
de corazón pero como iba diciendo estado
investigating okay and I don't want to pretend
investigando vale y no me las quiero dar
that I know the dates of
de que se sabe mejor la fecha de los
your relatives' deaths better than I do
fallecimientos de tus familiares que yo
but according to your photograph it will be different from
pero según tu fotografía distará las
your sister's photographs
fotografías de tu hermana
the stories because she uploaded stories in
las historias porque subió historias en
the cemetery okay we'll go then the
el cementerio vale eso iremos luego las
stories that you uploaded will install that
historias que subiste instalarán que la
people the network uploaded to youtube and the video
gente la red subió a youtube y el vídeo
that you uploaded just a month later they
que subiste justo un mes después me
tell me that your father passed away on
dicen que tu padre falleció el 16 de
July 16th this is the order of events
julio este es el orden de los sucesos
okay Luisito's WhatsApps communicate
valen los whatsapp de luisito comunica
with Rayito it supposedly belongs to
con rayito pertenecería supuestamente al
March 30th
30 de marzo
Felipe Rodriguez checking Redito's cell phone it was
felipe rodríguez revisando el móvil de
recorded on May 4th the video was
rédito se grabó el 4 de mayo el vídeo se
published on Ipe Rodriguez's Facebook on
publicó en el facebook del ipe rodríguez
July 14th therefore two days
el 14 de julio por lo tanto dos días
before the death of Redito's father
antes de la muerte del padre de réditos
and two months after recording it we
y dos meses después de grabarlo nos
started as Rayito is saying therefore
empecé como está diciendo rayito por lo
here the school already two lies
tanto aquí la escuela ya dos mentiras
regarding the publication dates of the
respecto a las fechas de publicación del
video in time antiquity since they
vídeo en el tiempo de antigüedad desde
recorded it until it was published  and
que lo grabaron hasta que lo público y
that coincided with the date of the
en que coincidió con la fecha de la
father's death and he does this because
muerte del padre y esto lo hace porque
then he's going to use the father's death
luego lo de la muerte del padre lo va a
as an excuse a bit, you see, it
utilizar un poco como excusa ya veréis
's like paperwork, not at the
es como de de papeleo no en la
Ministry of the Interior or that you have to check on
secretaría de gobernación o de que
your father's death, where are they
tienes que la defunción de tu papá donde
going to bury him, all that kind of
lo van a enterrar que todo ese tipo de
thing, and since I'm 12, since I had
cosas y yo como soy 12 como yo tenía
all the paperwork, I had already foreseen
todos los papeles ya yo había previsto
this situation, well, I was like the one
esta situación pues yo era el como el
responsible, so I was dealing with that issue and
responsable pues estaba con ese tema y
at the same time, well, with the
al mismo tiempo pues como con el
pending fact that everyone was writing to me,
pendiente de que todo mundo me escribía
how do I do it? I don't know how I resolve both
cómo le hago no sé cómo resuelvo ambas
situations, so in a video because of you,
situaciones entonces en un vídeo por tu
your friend is
culpa tu amigo
left looking unfaithful with his partner of
queda como infiel con su pareja de un
many years, I understand perfectly, I
montón de años entiendo perfectamente
can empathize with him that the father,
puedo empatizar con él en que el padre
even if it wasn't the day of his death, it
aunque no fuera el día de su muerte
was on the eve. I don't understand
estuviera en vísperas no entiendo que
those [ __ ] up moments, but it already smelled or it wasn't there,
esos momentos jodidos pero ya olía o no
Rayito, he had a conversation with
estaba rayito tenía una conversación con
which he could dismantle in a moment
la que podía desmontar en un momento
all the mess that was going on because the hell it
toda la que se estaba liando porque [__]
fell, whether it was because of William or whoever is, it's for a
se cayó sea por william o que esté es
lot, no matter how much is going on in
por mucho por mucho que esté pasando en
your family, it takes two minutes to
tu familia tardas dos minutos en
publish that conversation and the topic is
publicar esa conversación y el tema se
settled look guys the
queda zanjado mira chavales la
conversation was misread in the video
conversación se leyó mal en el vídeo en
actually like that however he didn't do it he
realidad así sin embargo no lo hizo
took more than a [ __ ] week to respond and to show the
tardó en responder y en enseñar la
conversation more
conversación más de una [__] semana más
than a [ __ ] week and the friend says it
de una [__] semana y dice el colega que
took a week because he had a
tardó una semana porque tuvo liado de
paperwork problem with the father with I don't know what
papeleo con lo del padre con no sé qué
lie
mentira
lie the first thing is that the day after
mentira lo primero es que el día después
his father's death one thing for
de la muerte de su padre una cosa por la
which he was heavily criticized rayito is because he
que fue muy criticada rayito es porque
was uploading stories throughout
estuvo subiendo historias durante todo
the funeral showing us how beautiful
el entierro enseñándonos lo bonito que
the cemetery was showing us the
era el cementerio enseñándonos el coche
hearse which is well each one each one
fúnebre que bueno cada uno cada uno
carries their things in their own way it doesn't
lleva sus cosas a su forma a mí no me
seem more appropriate to me but well each one
parece más adecuado pero bueno cada uno
there I'm going to respect it for each one
ahí lo voy a respetar para cada uno
kasper but you have time to make
kasper pero tienes tiempo de hacer
stories at the funeral burying your
historias en el funeral enterrando tu
father and your love is mobile like
padre y tu amor es móvil en plan
influence we follow the hearse
influencia vamos siguiendo la carroza
where the cemetery wanted to
donde el cementerio se los quería
show it to them which seemed very beautiful to me and you
mostrar que se me hizo muy bello y no
couldn't deny what your friend said in two
podías desmentir lo de tu amigo en dos
minutes by simply publishing the
minutos publicando simplemente la
conversation since it took two minutes
conversación ya que tardaban dos minutos
literally since the 14th how he misses the
literalmente desde el día 14 que extraña
controversy until the 23rd that he uploads
la polémica hasta el día 23 que el sube
these stories, I mean, he's a time cruncher,
estas historias o sea es un cojo de
I know he hasn't been able to and I tried to avoid
sé que no ha podido e intente evitar
talking about this topic because I didn't want to
hablar de este tema porque no quería
involve my friends more,
involucrar más a mis amigos
what's the point? I mean, your friend
qué sentido tiene hecho o sea a tu amigo
is getting all this heat that he
le está cayendo todo el chaparrón de que
's unfaithful because of you for having
es infiel por tu culpa de haber
collaborated on that video, to his girlfriend, who I
colaborado en ese vídeo a la novia que
imagine is also fond of him,
me imagino que también le tendrá cariño
no, because if your friend's girlfriend of so many years would
no porque si la novia de tantos años de
also know her, she's in
tu amigo también la conocería está en
zither stories, the girl crying
historias de cítara llorando la chavala
because she's having a bad time and you don't
porque lo está pasando mal y tú no
talk about the subject and he doesn't come out to deny it
hablar del tema y no sale a desmentirlo
because he doesn't want to involve them and make us
porque no quiere involucrarlos y
feel good, but I
sentirnos bien pero definitivamente ya
'm definitely tired of hearing bad
estoy cansado de estar escuchando malos
comments about something that isn't true and I'm
comentarios por algo que no es verdad y
going to clarify it for you right now, and
se los voy a aclarar en este momento y
if I hadn't clarified it before it's because I
si no lo había aclarado antes es porque
was with his personal stories and I didn't have the
estaba con a sus personales y no tuve la
opportunity to do it, I'm
oportunidad de hacerlo
lying, I've already said it, it's a lie, he was there
mentira ya lo he dicho es mentira estuvo
all week, apart from the stories he
toda la semana aparte de las historias
made at the funeral, uploading
que hizo en el entierro subiendo
stories with his girlfriend, uploading stories
historias con su novia subiendo
at the dentist, uploading
historias en el dentista subiendo
stories with friends, in fact he was
historias con amigos de hecho estuvo
tweeting every day, here he has a
tuiteando todos los días aquí tiene un
twitter  uploading four pictures with his
twitter subiendo cuatro fotitos con su
dog here another one and here a tweet making
perro aquí otro y aquí un tweet haciendo
the [ __ ] joke about the old man filter with
la [__] broma del filtro del viejito de
the comb pp already has time for this
la peina pp ya tiene tiempo para esta
[ __ ] [ __ ] to make the
[__] [__] para hacer el filtro del
old man filter and doesn't have time to deny
viejito y no tiene tiempo para desmentir
the accusations that are being made
las acusaciones que se le están haciendo
to your friend when you have the
a tu amigo cuando tienes las
conversations at hand sorry but I don't
conversaciones a mano perdona pero no me
believe it
lo creo
sorry but you're not lying now we
perdona pero no estás mintiendo ahora
will go on to interpret the
pasaremos a interpretar bien la
conversation well okay to wait since I
conversación vale esperar ya que lo
reviewed it three days later it was like I said
revise tres días después fue como dije
these messages are misread
estos mensajes están mal leídos
you you know they were sent and I had
tú tú lo sabes mandados y yo los había
sent them it doesn't have that it was good good I
mandado no tiene eso estuvo bien bien o
mean it gives us an idea of ​​the essence of what
sea nos da una idea de la esencia de lo
that channel was you haven't seen how it
que era ese canal no ha visto cómo
returns to its success on
vuelve a su éxito
that channel like taking advantage of
en ese canal en plan aprovechándose de
the bad reputation that badaboom has
la mala reputación que tiene badaboom
these friends rayito saying that
estas amigos rayito diciendo que a los
three days later I released the conversation
tres días saco la conversación
three days later it was like he says something that you
tres días después fue como dice cosa que
just saw that throws me that it took more
acabáis de ver que me tira que tardó más
than a week you are lying now they are
de una semana estás mintiendo ahora le
literally lying to him and there is still
están mintiendo literalmente y todavía
more they are very attentive to the click
hay más están muy atentos al clic de
now because suddenly they take into account
ahora porque de repente en cuenta toda
the whole history of what is said in that
la historia de lo que se dice en ese
chat  totally different from the one we
chat totalmente diferente a la que
read a year ago and then
leímos hace un año y entonces le
all the ones with which I have used
salieron todas las con las que he usado
or have used that word came out and you told me
o han usado esa palabra y tú me dijiste
here is the love that you caught you
aquí está el amor que te cogiste tú me
told me because you met a girl
dijiste porque te encontraste una chica
in a bar who said hello to you
en un bar que te saludo
and then you were like haha ​​the
y entonces tú me pusiste como jaja la
girl who caught me something like that
morra que me cogía algo así
the move is supposed to be
se supone que la movida sería
rayito slept with someone one
rayito se acostó con alguien una noche
crazy night and the next day it turns out that
loca y al día siguiente resulta ser que
that same woman met luisito
esa misma mujer se encontró con luisito
comunica at some place or whatever what's the
comunica en algún local o lo que sea no
point of you sleeping with
qué sentido tiene que tú te acuestes con
someone and the next day you meet
alguien y al día siguiente te encuentres
her friend and go to the girl and say
a su colega y vaya a la chica y le digas
luisito hi my name is macarena I'm the one who
luisito hola me llamo macarena yo soy la
met 5th friend yesterday it doesn't make
que se 5to colega ayer no tiene sentido
any sense but oh well the move that they are
ninguno pero bueno la movida que están
telling let's imagine what is
contando vamos a imaginar lo que es
true what it would be that rayito
verdad lo que sería esa rayito se
sleeps with a girl one night and the
acuesta con una chica una noche y al día
next day that girl meets
siguiente esa chica se encuentra con
luisito she greets them saying I was
luisito los saluda diciéndole yo estuve
with rayito last night and then luisito sends her a
con rayito anoche y entonces luisito le
whatsapp with a picture of the
manda un whatsapp con una foto de la
girl or something saying look who I
chica o algo diciéndole mira con quién
'm with with the girl over there but
estoy con la morra de allí pero es que
if we go to the conversation it's
si nos vamos a la conversación es
totally different okay here we see in
totalmente diferente vale aquí vemos en
the conversations good to know the
las conversaciones bueno saberlo la
conversation that on xv in the video I
conversación que el xv en el vídeo yo le
sent this video to Louis it's a video that
envié este vídeo a louis es un vídeo que
a girl I went out with sent me it
me envió pues una chica con la cual salí
's totally different it turns out that
es totalmente diferente resulta ser que
the girl he went out with before
la chica con la que salió de antes le
sends him a video okay she sends a video to
manda un vídeo vale le manda un vídeo a
Rayito and Rayito the trophy plan
rayito y rayito el plan trofeo se lo
forwards it to Luisito okay saying look at the one
reenvía a luisito vale diciendo mira la
who was holding me up and then like
que me cogía en pie y entonces como
some video well in the video she'll be seen
algún vídeo pues en el vídeo se le verá
hurt or whatever and Luisito says
perjudicada o lo que sea y luisito dice
ok it was up to no the truth and I
ok ya estaba hasta la no la verdad y yo
gave this nest to Luis and I put the one
le rendí este nido a luis y le puse la
that I bought I did it I sent it
que me compré yo lo hice yo se lo mandé
to him to which me and you told me here's
a él a lo cual yo y tú me dijiste aquí
the girl that you told me because
está la morra que tú me dijiste porque
you found a girl he answered me
te encontraste una chica él me respondió
all this that you see here and this is the
todo esto que ven aquí y esta es la
conversation I don't really know he's
conversación yo no sé realmente el is
red because he took it out of context  things and he
red porque sacó de contexto las cosas y
told me he didn't incite the rascal who
me dijo no incito el pillo la que le
caught him on the ground and I don't know why
cogía en tierra y yo no sé por qué todo
now a year later he's telling a
ahora un año después está contando una
totally different story I don't know if you
historia totalmente diferente no sé si
know one thing is worth it but for me the
sabéis una cosa vale pero a mí los años
boomer years and the years of experience have
de boomer y los años de experiencia pues
made me learn to know how to detect
me han hecho aprender a saber detectar
when someone is lying there's no
cuando alguien está mintiendo no hace
need
falta
when they want to make up a story to
cuando te quiere inventar una historia
study it a lot a lot a
que te la estudie mucho mucho mucho
lot in the end they end up running into a
mucho al final terminan corriendo te una
contradiction because when you're
contradicción porque cuando tú estás
telling the truth you simply have to
diciendo la verdad simplemente tienes
remember remember what happened and you're
que recordar recordar lo que pasó y
always going to tell the same thing because
siempre vas a contar lo mismo porque
how you're telling the truth you're always
cómo estás contando la verdad siempre
going to tell the same the same
vas a contar los mismos los mismos
details you're never going to say one thing that
detalles nunca vas a decir una cosa que
contradicts the other but when you're
contradiga a la otra pero cuando estás
making up the story then in a year you
inventar la historia luego dentro un año
don't remember the story well and you have to
no te acuerdas bien de la historia y la
tell it again live
tienes que volver a contar en un directo
and in the end you make a mistake in a detail
y al final te equivocas en un detalle
that contrary to last year that's why you should
que contrario al del año pasado
n't lie and the truth is
por eso no hay que mentir y la verdad es
that let's see if I'm very sincere and also
que a ver si soy muy sincero y también
with people use by the time all that
con la gente usa para cuando todo eso
happened I had even broken up with her
pasó yo incluso ya había terminado con
with Leo Sayer we were no longer
con su leo sayer ya no éramos novios de
left-wing boyfriends  I mean, everything's fine between her and
izquierda o sea todo bien entre ella y
I, the truth is that I
yo todo que la verdad es que igual no te
can't tell you that it affected me or anything, it's
puedo decir que me afectó ni nada está
another lie, guys, he says, Licito says that
otra mentira chavales dice lícito que
when everything happened he wasn't with his
cuando pasó todo no estaba ya con la
girlfriend anymore, we were talking live and seeing the
chule contábamos en directo y viendo los
comments on my live stream, well, it makes me
comentarios de mi directo pues me da
realize that there are two types of people who
cuenta que hay dos tipos de personas que
interpret these in two different ways,
interpretan estos de dos formas
there are people who interpret that when
hay personas que interpretan que cuando
Luisito says that he was no longer with his
luisito dice que ya no estaba con la
girlfriend when what happened happened, he's referring
chule cuando pasó lo que pasó se refiere
to the messages, okay, when he had the
a los mensajes vale a cuando tuvo la
conversation, we'll be talking about the fact
conversación ya estaremos hablando de
that in March they weren't together, at the end of
que ya en marzo no estaban a finales de
March he was no longer together,
marzo ya no estaba
certain people understand that he's
cierta gente que entiende como que está
saying that he was no longer with his girlfriend
diciendo que ya no estaba con la chule
at the time the video was published,
en el momento que se publicó el vídeo o
meaning from July 14th, I think it
sea a partir del 14 de julio yo creo que
was after the video, I'm not going to
fue después a raíz del vídeo no te voy a
tell you either that the alleged
decir tampoco que la supuesta
infidelity was the cause of the breakup,
infidelidad fuera la causa de la ruptura
but maybe it was the trigger, it
pero tal vez que fuera el detonante
could be, it could be. Here we have a
puede ser puede ser aquí tenemos una
photo of the cat's tongue, of all these, he
foto de lengua del gato de todas estas
publishes on his Instagram, okay, from
publica en su instagram vale del 6 de
April 6th it would be after the WhatsApps,
abril sería posterior a los whatsapp
but Rayito still hadn't recorded the
pero todavía rayito no había grabado el
video  for free okay cat tongue says
vídeo por libre vale lengua de gato dice
always loving you never in loving you
siempre amándote nunca in amándote
illicit communicates says always yours
ilícito comunica dice siempre tuyo
never I sense it I see it here very well does not
nunca intuyo yo lo veo aquí muy bien no
see them here with any intention of
los ve aquí con ninguna intención de
breaking up or that they were going through a
cortar ni que estuvieran pasando por una
crisis but at least what it appears
crisis pero por lo menos lo que aparenta
not but let's say that together there are these
no pero vamos que juntos están estas
photos from May 9th or even
fotos del 9 de mayo o sea incluso
after Rayito and Lizbeth
posterior a que rayito y lizbeth
recorded the video okay he puts a
grabarán el vídeo vale le pone a que un
romantic message to the one who visited Comunica and
mensaje romántico al visitó comunica y
Luisito Comunica says thank you for
luisito comunica le dice gracias por
accompanying me on this trip I urgently needed to
acompañarme en este viaje me urgía
fill another page of this
llenar otra hoja de este álbum tan
beautiful album of experiences with you I don't know
bonito de experiencias contigo yo no sé
how to interpret this but I
ustedes cómo interpretar esto pero yo lo
interpret it to me they are still together on
interpreta me están juntos todavía el 9
May 9th five days after the recitation
de mayo cinco días después de que recite
live recorded in the video and well for
live grabarse en el vídeo y bueno para
the people who interpreted it as
la gente que la interpretado como
saying that when the video was published they were
diciendo que cuando se publicó el vídeo
no longer together here we have these
ya no estaban juntos aquí tenemos estas
photos on Luisito's Instagram
fotos en el instagram de luisito
Comunica in it they
comunica en él
communicated days before
comunicaban días antes de que se
the video was published today or a good day to
publique el vídeo hoy o un buen día para
tell this young lady that I admire her and I
decirle a esta señorita que la admiro y
am very proud of her I am sorry it is that
estoy muy orgulloso de ella lo siento es
I am happy with life for having become
que estoy feliz con la vida por haberme
a part of the  yours
hecho una parte de la tuya
joy macarena was on the
alegría macarena estuvo en el equipo de
comments team whatever you want how you
los comentarios lo que queráis cómo lo
interpret it and you I interpreted it
interpreta y ustedes yo lo interpretó
as if they broke up after the
como que han cortado después de la
whole thing and well the breakup was made official
movida y bueno se hace oficial la
exactly at the beginning of
ruptura exactamente a principios de
September of the same year after
septiembre del mismo año después de
summer a couple of months later not
verano un par de meses después no
only freaked out that luisito
solamente flipado con que luisito
mientras and he made up with his [ __ ] face
mientras y se invente por la [__] cara
that he wasn't with her anymore when
que ya no estaba con ella cuando pasó
all this happened but he also had the nerve to
todo esto sino que ha tenido la cara de
say that it didn't affect him the same no I
decir que no le afectó igual no no te
can't tell you that it affected me or anything so
puedo decir que me afectó ni nada así
very affected
que muy afectada
if it doesn't affect you to see a person
si no te afecta ver así a una persona
with whom you have shared your life for
con la que ha compartido la vida
so many years
tantísimos años
really
de verdad
the truth of all this anyway
la verdad de todo esto de todas maneras
business ways many comments
empresariales muchos comentarios
and in that activity they don't know what it's like to
y en esa actividad no saben cómo es
have relationships to be published
tener relaciones ser publicados
stop trying less
dejen de intentar menos
and I want to have a little stone you have a
y quiero tener un poco de piedra tienen
stone face air of stone both
la cara de piedra aire de piedra las dos
things liar and shameless and I've already done
cosas mentiroso y caradura y ya he hecho
what's coming now it's going to be the festival
que viene ahora va a ser el festival
okay
vale
sasin have you had enough it's still like
sasin habéis tenido suficiente todavía
this I still don't know satisfied don't think
es así todavía no sé conforme no penséis
that a movie is being made that has
que se esté montando una peli que tenga
acting in squeezing your glutes hard
actuando en apretar fuerte los glúteos
there that you
ahí que se os pongan durito pero pero
put it hard but but hard hard hard that I can put there on top of the west a glass of water with a rum and coke squeeze and hard but gosh I want I want to tell you friend he distances me a little because maybe I felt with that action like wait Ryan Arista in an unstable situation
ryan arista en una situación inestable
maybe dangerous no then it's better if we
tal vez peligrosa no entonces mejor
let the brother fix his things
dejemos que el brother arregle sus cosas
and then we continue talking no and let's see
y luego nos seguimos hablando no y a ver
what a little distraction from him that Luisito
que se distracción poco de él que
used a little of the profits
utilización un poco luisito de réditos
because as Rayito was in that
porque como rayito estaba en ese momento
bad moment because his father had died well he
malo porque se había muerto el padre
kind of gave him air and let him
pues como que le dejó aire y le dejó
breathe to relax with him to
respirar se hacerse distensión con él
do him a favor I think that in
por hacerle un favor yo creo que en
truth he distanced himself because Luisito
verdad se distanció por que luisito
Comunica was at that moment
comunica estaba en ese momento
interpreting the role of Sonic and since he
interpretando el papel de sonic y como
was in a hurry he took off I'm going to leave I'm going to
era el prisa se quitó voy a dejar voy a
let see the jokes okay yes it's
dejar ver los chistes vale sí que es
true that Luisito Comunica I don't know
verdad que a luisito comunicar no sé
how it happened because I haven't seen the
cómo se le dio porque no he visto la
Latin American version I don't know how it
versión latinoamericana no sé cómo se le
happened he plays Sony but come on he's
dio interpreta a la sony pero vamos este
playing this role like a total pain I almost
papel lo está haciendo de culo casi que
believed him to be better than life you are  I was
me creía más que la vida tú eres estaba
pregnant it's supposed to be that if you
embarazada sea se supone que si tú
love your friend who isn't fighting
quieres a tu colega que no está peleado
with him is fine it's cool with him and his
con él está bien está guay con él y se
father just died it's supposed to be that
acaba de morir el padre se supone que
when it is most needed maybe not you didn't
que que cuando más se necesita quizá no
do it you were mad at him you
no lo hiciste tú estabas enfadado con él
unfollowed him on instagram and I don't
lo dejaste de seguir en instagram y no
know if on social media you stopped
sé si en las redes sociales dejaste de
recording with him
grabar con él
the series that you were doing whenever I
la serie que estabas haciendo siempre
recorded them with him the series made of
que las grababa con él la serie hecha de
the cheapest and most expensive motels
los moteles más baratos y más caros
sharing content stopped being seen
tiene compartir contenido dejó de verse
for profit on your social media when
a rédito por tus redes sociales cuando
rayito was very frequent very insistent
rayito era muy frecuente muy insistente
in the comments of your face in each
en los comentarios de tu cara en cada
photo and suddenly the dry one did
foto y de repente el seco
n't follow him and wasn't interested who are they
no le seguía y no interesaba a quien
trying to fool dude now seriously and I'm
quieren engañar tío ya ya en serio y te
going to remind you of the famous video that you
voy a recordar el famoso vídeo que
uploaded a few months later saying hey
subiste unos meses después diciendo es
this is public so subtle okay that
ésta está pública tan sutil vale que
none of us get it here you have it I have
ninguno captamos aquí la tenéis he
also learned that there are people who
aprendido también que hay personas que
even if you know they are not
aunque tú sepas que no son mal
malicious and even if you know that they are
intencionadas y aunque tú sepas que son
good people it's better to keep them a
buenas personas está mejor tenerlas un
little distanced because even if their
poquito distanciadas porque aunque sus
intentions are not bad and even if
intenciones no sean malas y aunque los
you love them very much and appreciate them like you
quieras muchísimo y los aprecies como no
have no idea there are people  that maybe they are
tienes idea hay personas que tal vez te
going to cause you problems and you have to know how to
van a causar problemas y hay que saber
recognize it and you have to know how to mark
reconocerlo y hay que saber marcar
a certain small barrier even if it is for a
cierta pequeña barrera aunque sea por un
while with these people that is useful is
tiempo con estas personas que es útil es
that it is useful itself not fashionable show and do
que es útil mismo no de moda muestra y
not prune anyone for alluding to spam or
no poda a nadie por aludido al spam o
rays that it is better to have television or
rayitos que más vale tener tele o
listen to rita done that not even with a stick from a
escuchar hecho rita que ni con un palo a
distance in the hypothetical case that this
distancia en el hipotético caso que esto
was not for rayito what a joke but
no fuera por rayito que de coña pero
well let's give housing to our
bueno vamos a darle vivienda a nuestra
imagination okay this has not gone for
imaginación vale que esto no ha ido por
profits in the hypothetical case that it
réditos en el hipotético caso que no
was not for profits and everyone in the
fuera por réditos y todo el mundo en la
street comments on your video and
calle comentario de tu vídeo y en toda
everywhere is taking rayito for granted and
parte está dando por aludido a rayito y
you would be cool with him I'm not telling you to
tú estuviera guay con él no te digo que
go out and speak out against this kid it's
salgas a pronunciarse a este chaval es
not for profit that it goes for but the
que no va por rédito que va por pero lo
best thing to see make a gesture so that
mejor a ver echar un gesto para que la
people will say no no few profits but I did not
gente dirá no no pocos réditos pero no
do it that you did not even follow them because you are
lo hice que ni los seguías porque estás
putting man I mean I do not know why they are
metiendo tío o sea yo no sé por qué
really lying I do not know what to
realmente están mintiendo yo no sé que
believe because really that of
creerme porque realmente que de la de
Badajoz of the clean  Rodriguez is with
badajoz de la limpia rodríguez está con
the liars with the [ __ ] that he has
los mentirosa que con la de [__] que
done to people is that I can not
ha hecho a la gente es que no me puedo
believe absolutely anything but what is very
creer absolutamente nada pero es que lo
clear to me
que tengo clarísimo
after seeing this time is that you
después de ver esta época es que todos
are all lying too, so at the
estás mintiendo también entonces al
end of the story one way or
final de la historia de una manera ni
the other it will surely be a
será de la otra aquí seguramente haya
cat here and it is not the sea of ​​​​the
gato encerrado y no son las sea del
actur you know what happens
actur sabéis qué es lo que pasa que
when a person is already so
cuando una persona está ya tan
labeled and so pointed out in the networks
etiquetada y tan señalada en las redes
is already sexist it is very difficult to
ya es sexista es muy difícil que se lo
remove it I have put you in the last
quite os he puesto en los últimos
live the same example always but the fact is that he
directos el mismo ejemplo siempre pero
completely exposed the pool boys not with
completamente a los piscineros no con
the [ __ ] garbage behind him was doing
las [__] basura detrás estaba haciendo
with the page the headphones all
con la página los auriculares toda
[ __ ] and they did not cancel them they continue
[__] y no los cancelaron siguen
uploading videos it is normal because because it
subiendo vídeos es normal porque porque
was Talas if instead of Dallas it had
era talas si en vez de dallas lo llega a
been Rodriguez's letter this or
ser la carta de rodríguez ésta o
any quality of any person
cualquier calidad de cualquier persona
who was loved in the youtuber environment
que fuese querida en el entorno youtuber
and approved by everyone then
y aprobada por todo el mundo pues
surely they would have smoked it but that it
seguramente lo hubieran fumado pero que
was such a thing people put themselves in that they
fuera tal así la gente se pone que
thought truth to the always wonder
pensaba verdad a la siempre se pregunta
the world searches for dedicated and  monetize
el mundo busca por dedicado y monetiza
because they didn't take it seriously and no and they don't
pues no lo tomaron en serio y no y no
cancel people for how to clean up
cancelan a la gente por cómo limpiar
Rodriguez Ibarra boom they already have the
rodríguez ibarra boom tienen ya la
reputation they have because these people
reputación que tienen pues esta gente
are playing with the reputation and they are
están jugando con la reputación y están
taking advantage of it
aprovechándola
to clean themselves of the video of the dead man on
a limpiarse de vídeo del muerto de
top but the truth is I said like
encima pero la verdad yo dije así como
wave don't underestimate the judgment of people a little
wave no se subestimen un poco el juicio
because I like wyeth and I
a la gente porque yo como que wyeth y
said like they are not going to believe in the
dije así como no van a creta en el
genome of sense the salaries and I said dude
genoma de sentido los sueldos y dije wey
nobody believes this bum chick
nadie le cree a esta morra de vagabundos
everyone knows that her program is fake she's
todos saben que su programa es falso se
water and it doesn't belong to anyone anyone is going to believe her
agua y no es de nadie le va a creer el
time has made me learn one thing and that
tiempo me ha hecho aprender una cosa y
is that in the end a person who is very
es que al final una persona que sea muy
bad or who has done many things very
mala o que han hecho muchas cosas muy
wrong or who is not a liar does not have to
mal o que sin persona mentirosa no tiene
not be able to tell a serious truth
por qué no poder decir una verdad grave
and a person who is very loved who
y una persona que sea muy querida que
is very well seen and who is very social
esté muy bien vista y que sea muy social
and all their loss may sometimes sneak in
y todo su pierda puede que alguna vez se
and lie to you but since you trust
les cuele y te mienta pero como confía
him then you believe him and in the end if we
en él pues te lo crees y al final si nos
get with her well these two also
ponemos con ella pues estos dos también
have their history it's because we go the
tienen su historial es porque vamos el
ray of  infertility fact is a raffle
rayito de esterilidad hecho es un sorteo
that he did by giving us an iPhone live
que hizo soltándonos iphone en directo
okay
vale
raya showed more live and revealed more
raya mostró demás en vivo y reveló más
before the winners
antes de los a los ganadores
basically
básicamente
the rayito was in a live tweet
el rayito estaba en un directo de tuit
giving us iPhones he was going to say the
soltándonos iphones iba a decir los
winners you can see here the blog of it is not
ganadores se le ve aquí el blog de no
done with a bunch of numbers
está hecho con un montón de numeritos
written down his face to face breaks down
apuntado se le descompone la cara a cara
[Music] he
[Música]
is crazy because it goes to light
está loco porque se vaya a la luz
after that he acted like he had a failure
después de eso hizo como que tuvo fallo
in the sprint and ended the live and
en el sprint y termino el directo y lo
deleted it from the entire platform where he was
borró de toda la plataforma en donde
training so that there would be no
estaba entrenando para que no hubiera el
record of the failure he showed
registro del fallo demostró
in the notepad he had written down the
en el bloc de notas tenía apuntado los
numbers
números
he was drawing the iPhones and the
él estaba sorteando los iphones y los
winners were being drawn with a
ganadores los estaba sacando con una
numbering in theory at random with a
numeración en teoría al azar con una
page like this one there are of random numbers
página de esta que hay de números al
on google okay for the raffles that
azar en google vale para los sorteos que
these are done by guys I didn't have many
esto lo hacen muchachos tuve ni mucho
influences and he had
influences y él tenía en un bloc de
the numbers written down there in a notepad before the
notas los números apuntado ahí antes de
first winner came out and the second
que saliera primer ganador y segundo
before they chose him in the
antes de que lo escogieran en el número
random number here you have the number of a
al azar aquí tenéis el número de un
winner
ganador
and that corresponds to the number that comes out
y que corresponde con el número que sale
there in the notepad
ahí en el bloc de notas
and here you have the other one and also a
y aquí tienen el otro y además una cosa
curious thing to add here is that here it is
curiosa añadir aquí es que el aquí está
putting as maximum 1 to 40,000 and
poniendo como máximo del 1 al 40.000 y
here comes 302 1808 making a draw
sale aquí el 302 1808 haciendo un sorteo
a little strange there this well I leave it there I don't I don't
un poco ahí raro esto bueno ahí lo dejo
know what was left the thing there were many
no no sé qué quedó la cosa hubo muchos
youtubers who criticized this even
youtubers que criticaron esto incluso
werevertumorro made a parody of it and
werevertumorro le hizo una parodia y
everything is very reliable very reliable the draw did
todo sea muy fiable muy fiable el sorteo
not seem to do and luisito communicates well
no parecía hacer y luisito comunica pues
although nothing has been proven but it
aunque tampoco se ha probado nada pero
is true that on many
sí que es verdad que ya en muchas
occasions girls have come out when they decide
ocasiones han salido chavalas al decidir
that they had seen him being unfaithful to the
que le habían visto serle infiel a la
chick in clubs at parties or when he had one too many
chule en discotecas en fiesta o cuando
drinks this of course has not been
se pasaba de copa esto por supuesto no
confirmed but hey if we get into
se ha confirmado pero oye si nos ponemos
the rumors we put them with the
con los rumores los ponemos con los
gossip we get into everyone here
chismes nos ponemos con todos aquí
surely we all have a little
seguro que todos tenemos un poquito de
dust under the table - iron blogs that
polvo debajo de la mesa - iron blogs que
the dust is on his channel and nothing
el polvo lo tiene en su canal y nada
kids well up to here my tests
chavales pues hasta aquí mis pruebas
up to here
hasta aquí
argument and my theory my theories and what I do
argumento y mi teoría mis teorías y lo
not know if you agree
que no sé si vaya está de acuerdo
with me or  they are reading the
conmigo o se están leyendo la caja de
comment box of course I respect all
comentarios por supuesto respeto todas
your opinions even those of you
vuestras opiniones hasta de los fans de
cat fans who are going to come to defend the
gatos que vais a venir a defender lo
indefensible whatever it is I insist I have
indefendible sea como sea insisto no
nothing against either of these
tengo nada en contra de ninguno de estos
two in fact more or less what they do on the
dos de hecho más o menos lo que hacen en
internet seems like a wine to me it transmits in
internet me parece un wine transmite en
both very good vibes it has been their
los dos muy buen rollo ha sido su
work it transmits very good vibes to me they
trabajo transmite muy buena onda me
seem like very happy guys they will
parece unos chicos muy alegre que
have their ups and downs like everyone else
tendrán sus más y sus menos como todo el
I dislike the ones from bala won the most I have
mundo me cae peor los de bala won
always said it but it is that in this
siempre lo he dicho pero es que en este
case I believe that these people are
caso yo creo que esta gente se están
inventing part of the story here and
inventando aquí parte de la historia y
nothing is simply I am wrong it may
nada es simplemente me equivoco puede
be I am handsome but I am not
ser soy guapo pero tampoco soy
gifted either it depends on what
superdotado depende en qué
we see weed
nos vemos hierba